that ICICI Lombard General Insurance
Company Limited fell by 3.6 percent today. The
result behind this fall will be known in Pimple. Before going to Pimple, you
can see how the system has given returns in the last some time. So, there was a
fall of 36 percent today and the reason for this fall is that
due to which I have subscribed to the stock person today on this topic
and close it in 5 minutes.
Your money has doubled in this stock.
Prabhu has done a little more. So in the long run, the
stock has given good money. 19th of
that and even on January 1, 2021, till now, this system has
not given any special return, but
in a year, I will do it on Saturday. The return has gone in the system,
which was
subscribed by clicking. There is a good boom in the market.
General Insurance
means that initially,
this front insurance term
insurance
[music] has been made an
app to dance that now through active heart,
so despite the boom in the market, this is the
reason why the system fell
and let's see 20. Do
not forget to share through two days and
[music] by
clicking on the subscribe button
which is of Tuesday  The day was done
through a computer company
and
it is known that there was a decline in the system
and this indicative price is to be avoided by people through heart,
more than 100 shares
and
subscribe
long term investment is an excellent stock
and
this is the position that we should fold, it can
give good returns, if you liked the video then
like and subscribe to the channel
and
[Music]